{
    "subject": "resource/Baruch_Kamin",
    "predicate": "property/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Bilhorod-Dnistrovskyi",
    "human_readable": "Baruch Kamin was born in Bilhorod-Dnistrovskyi.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8751455545425415,
            "question": "Where was Baruch Kamin born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8513891696929932,
            "question": "Were there any famous people born in Bilhorod-Dnistrovskyi?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8053660988807678,
            "question": "What year was Baruch Kamin born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.623340368270874,
            "question": "What is Bilhorod-Dnistrovskyi known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6138131618499756,
            "question": "In what country is Bilhorod-Dnistrovskyi located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5685155391693115,
            "question": "What is Baruch Kamin known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5242473483085632,
            "question": "What is the history of Bilhorod-Dnistrovskyi?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45067915320396423,
            "question": "Is there any information about Baruch Kamin's family?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4474589228630066,
            "question": "Can you find any historical events related to Bilhorod-Dnistrovskyi?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41897380352020264,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Baruch Kamin?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Baruch Kamin was born in Bilhorod-Dnistrovskyi.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3012_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you find any historical events related to Bilhorod-Dnistrovskyi?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3012_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any information about Baruch Kamin's family?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3012_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the history of Bilhorod-Dnistrovskyi?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3012_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3012_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3012_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3012_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3012_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3012_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3012_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3012_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3012_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3012_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3012_70.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the provided context information, I found that:\n\n* There is no mention of a person named \"Baruch Kamin\" being born in Bilhorod-Dnistrovskyi. In fact, there are two mentions of Baruch Kamin, but both state that he was born in Poland, not Bilhorod-Dnistrovskyi.\n* The context information does contain some mention of Bilhorod-Dnistrovskyi and its historical significance, but it is unrelated to the birthplace of Baruch Kamin.\n\nBased on this analysis, I conclude that:\n\n`{'output': 'no'}`"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: None of the provided documents mention that Baruch Kamin was born in Bilhorod-Dnistrovskyi. The information given is about his role in the Israeli independence movement and his involvement with the Haganah, but there is no reference to his birthplace being Bilhorod-Dnistrovskyi."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Baruch Kamin was born in Poland, not Bilhorod-Dnistrovskyi.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The provided text describes Baruch Kamin's life and origins, stating he was born in Poland and immigrated to Israel.  There is no mention of Bilhorod-Dnistrovskyi in his biography.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The claim is wrong because Baruch Kamin was born in Poland in 1918.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information does not mention Baruch Kamin being born in Bilhorod-Dnistrovskyi. Furthermore, the details provided about his birthplace indicate he was born in Poland, specifically in Kamin-Kushirski, Volhyn.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}